what is the Network+ certification
什么是 Network+ 认证
let's go ahead and find out
让我们找出答案
hey everybody this is Zach with IT career questions
大家好，这里是 Zach回答 IT 职业问题
and today we are answering what is the Network+ certification
今天我们来回答一下什么是Network+认证
if you haven't checked out the A+ certification video
如果您还没有查看 A+ 认证视频
go ahead and click on this link somewhere around here
继续并单击此处附近的此链接
and it was our previous video about answering CompTIA certification questions
这是我们之前关于回答 CompTIA 认证问题的视频
this video specifically targets the Network+ certification
该视频专门针对 Network+ 认证
what is it what do I need to know about it why am I going to take it
这是什么我需要知道什么我为什么要考它
so the Network+ certification again is a certification that is brought to you by CompTIA
所以 Network+ 认证又是 CompTIA 带给你的认证
you check out CompTIA or I'll put that link in the description below
你查看 CompTIA 或者我会将该链接放在下面的描述中
the Network+ certification is an excellent certification to get
Network+ 认证是获得的优秀认证
if you are looking to get some type of networking position
如果您正在寻找某种类型的网络职位
if you don't have a broad knowledge base of networking
如果您没有广泛的网络知识库
or even if you do have a broad knowledge base of networking
或者即使您确实拥有广泛的网络知识库
if you're looking for that networking job
如果您正在寻找网络工作
you might want to look at getting your network plus certification
您可能想看看获得您的网络加认证
definitely is a go-to as far as networking certifications go
就网络认证而言，绝对是首选
and if you don't have a degree
如果你没有学位
you can definitely fall back on a network plus certification
您绝对可以依靠网络加认证
because it is pretty good
因为它很好
and of course once you do the Network+ certification
当然，一旦您完成了 Network+ 认证
you can go off and get your CCNA and all those things
你可以去拿你的CCNA和所有这些东西
you don't have to have a college degree to get any of these certifications
您不必拥有大学学位即可获得任何这些证书
which is definitely very excellent if that's not the route that you took
如果那不是您所走的路线，那绝对是非常好的
even if you do have a college degree
即使你有大学学位
it's still suggested that you get some of these certifications
仍然建议您获得其中一些认证
because employers love to see that stuff
因为雇主喜欢看那些东西
anyway the Network+ certification covers everything
无论如何，Network+ 认证涵盖了一切
networking right switches VLANs land lands access points
网络权 交换机 VLAN 陆地 陆地 接入点
whatever it is that has to do with networking
不管是什么与网络有关
you will learn with the Network+ certification
您将通过 Network+ 认证学习
as i talked about in my previous video
正如我在之前的视频中所说的那样
if you are looking for lots of great information
如果您正在寻找大量重要信息
and want to learn more about the Network+ certifications
并想了解有关 Network+ 认证的更多信息
go ahead and check out professor masters youtube channel
去看看教授大师 youtube 频道
he has lots of great material over there
他那里有很多很棒的材料
and he will give you lots of great examples
他会给你很多很好的例子
of how the Network+ certification tests are laid out
Network+ 认证测试的布局方式
and basically goes start to finish with all that stuff
基本上是从所有这些东西开始到结束
so check him out for now I can give you guys a couple of examples of Network+ certifications
所以现在检查他我可以给你们几个网络+认证的例子
that you may receive on the test
您可能会在测试中收到
again keep in mind
再次记住
there are so many questions to this test
这个测试有很多问题
that no test is exactly the same
没有测试是完全相同的
it's not entirely true but there's so many different versions of the test
这并不完全正确，但测试有很多不同的版本
that you will take that you know they just mix up the questions and things like that
你会认为你知道他们只是把问题和类似的事情混为一谈
so a couple questions here I'm going to do three of them
所以这里有几个问题我要做三个
one is a user's remote marketing server has changed IP address schemes
一是用户的远程营销服务器更改了IP地址方案
and now the user can no longer access it the user
现在用户不能再访问它了
the user for further discovers that the distant
用户进一步发现了问题
and still has access to them
并且仍然可以访问它们
which of the following is a possible cause
以下哪一项是可能的原因
so again this is all multiple choice
所以这又是多项选择
so A is SNMP strings need to be added
所以 A 是需要添加的 SNMP 字符串
B firewall rules need to be configured
B 需要配置防火墙规则
C port bonding on the interface needs to be enabled
C需要启用接口上的端口绑定
D the switch has lost power
D 开关掉电
so multiple choice what would you go with
所以多项选择你会选择什么
if you said B firewall rules need to be configured
如果你说B防火墙规则需要配置
that's the right answer so something
这是正确的答案
happened with the firewall
发生在防火墙上
where it lost configuration
丢失配置的地方
maybe nobody ever configured it
也许没有人配置过它
so you're gonna have to go ahead and configure that firewall
所以你必须继续配置防火墙
and see how that needs to be set up
看看需要如何设置
in order for this user to access the marketing server
为了让该用户访问营销服务器
the next question is which of the following is a network device
下一个问题是以下哪个是网络设备
that allows remote users access to a network
允许远程用户访问网络
A DNS server
一个 DNS 服务器
B content filter
B 内容过滤器
C load balancer
C 负载均衡器
D VPN concentrator
D VPN集中器
so based off this multiple choice question
所以基于这个多项选择题
I know the answer do you know the answer
我知道答案你知道答案吗
if you said D VPN concentrator
如果你说 D VPN 集中器
that's correct you will use a VPN connection to remotely access your work Business Network
没错，您将使用 VPN 连接远程访问您的工作业务网络
so that's second example of a network plus certification question
这是网络加认证问题的第二个例子
that you could receive on the test
你可以在测试中碰到
that you may go out and take
的问题
third and last question that we'll go over is a technician suspects
我们要讨论的第三个也是最后一个问题是技术人员怀疑
that a virus has been introduced on the network
病毒已被引入网络
which network resources is best used to confirm this problem
最好使用哪些网络资源来确认这个问题
A syslog
系统日志
B SNMP
C network sniffer
C 网络嗅探器
and D environmental monitor
D 环境监测器
if you said C network sniffer you're right
如果你说 C 网络嗅探器你是对的
you are going to use this tool to basically sniff out any problems
你将使用这个工具来基本发现任何问题
that you may have on the network
您可能在网络上拥有的
so these are the three examples that I gave you on
这就是我给你的三个例子
questions that you may receive on the Network+ certification test
您可能会在 Network+ 认证测试中碰到的问题
the Network+ certification test is a great thing to study for
Network+ 认证考试是值得学习的好东西
because it really does give you a broad example of how an entire network works
因为它确实为您提供了一个关于整个网络如何工作的广泛示例
it starts you from the very beginning until almost towards the end
它从一开始就开始直到几乎结束
it's not going to go too far into the security things
它不会在安全方面太深入
and and how a lot of more complex things are set up
以及如何设置许多更复杂的东西
so don't go and take a network plus certification test
所以不要去参加网络加认证测试
and expect that you're going to be like a network administrator right off the bat
并期望您立即成为一名网络管理员
that's probably not going to happen
这可能不会发生
you definitely have to get years of experience
你一定要有多年的经验
on basically how networks are actually set up
基本上关于网络的实际设置方式
you know every business is completely different from one another
你知道每一项业务都彼此完全不同
every business uses completely different equipment sometimes
每个企业有时使用完全不同的设备
you know you might have HP curse
你知道你可能有HP curse
which is you might have Cisco switches
你可能有思科交换机
who knows
谁知道
so you might need to know how each different brand configures their switches
所以你可能需要知道每个不同品牌如何配置他们的交换机
and how all that stuff works
以及所有这些东西是如何工作的
so again Network+ certification great thing to study for
所以网络+认证又是值得学习的好东西
again I kind of talked about this in the previous video on the A+ certification
再次，我在之前关于 A+ 认证的视频中谈到了这一点
you should actually also get your A+ certification
您实际上还应该获得 A+ 认证
because that's really going to give you a strong backbone of computers
因为那真的会给你一个强大的计算机支撑
and a little bit of networking but it's a really powerful thing that you should learn
还有一点网络，但这是你应该学习的非常强大的东西
because it's lots of knowledge
因为有很多知识
and if you are not familiar with how computers and networks and all that stuff works
如果您不熟悉计算机和网络以及所有这些东西的工作原理
or you're not too comfortable with it
或者你不太适应
these are two really good tests that you guys can take and get certified for
这是两个非常好的测试，你们可以参加并获得认证
and you guys will become employable
你们会很容易找工作
right after you do that test you are almost able to go out and get a job right away
在你做完那个测试后，你几乎可以马上出去找工作
just based off those certifications
仅凭这些认证
people love to see these certifications
人们喜欢看到这些认证
they really say oh this person does actually know a lot about network
他们真的说哦，这个人实际上对网络了解很多
they went out and got their Network+ certification
他可是获得了 Network+ 认证啊
that's not an easy that's not an easy certification to get by any means
这不是一件容易的事 无论如何都不是一件容易获得的认证
because there's a lot of studying involved and you need to know lots of things
因为涉及很多学习，你需要知道很多事情
and that's mainly because the test that you're going to take
这主要是因为你要参加的考试
could be completely different the next time that you were to take it
复考时可能会完全不同（这不废话么）
so you failed the first test and you go to take the next test
所以你第一次考试不及格，你去参加下一次考试
like man I remembered all the questions that I failed on this first test
你这样说 hey man 我记得我在第一次测试中失败的所有问题
then you go to this to take the second test over again right
然后你去复考
questions are completely different
问题完全不同
every single one is completely different
每一个都完全不同
so just you know if you're looking to get a certification the Network+ certification specifically
所以只要您知道您是否希望获得认证 Network+ 认证
do your studying go check out professor Messer great resource
做你的学习去看看梅塞尔教授很好的资源
to learn a lot about the Network+ and just networking in general
了解有关 Network+ 和一般网络的很多信息
so I hope this answers part of the question about the Network+ certification
所以我希望这能回答有关 Network+ 认证的部分问题
I will go into broader detail and actually show you guys examples
我将更详细地介绍并实际向你们展示示例
in the future as you guys know I'm working on the server setup
将来你们知道我正在处理服务器设置
and I haven't had time to do a lot of those videos
我没有时间做很多这些视频
I apologize for that
我为此道歉
but I will be trying to get as many of those videos put out as I possibly can
但我会尽可能多地发布这些视频
it's really hard to do those videos
做这些视频真的很难
because they do take a lot of time to do
因为他们确实需要很多时间来做
but bear with me I will get to them just as I will get to you more networking videos
请给我点时间，我可以的，就像我会制作更多的网络视频一样
and how you can set up a switch and how you can set up a VLAN and all that fun stuff
以及如何设置交换机以及如何设置 VLAN 以及所有有趣的东西
so you guys have any questions you know what to do
所以你们有任何问题你知道该怎么做
hit me up in the comments below
在下面的评论中@我
be more than happy to chat with you about anything you guys have questions about
非常乐意与您聊聊你们有任何疑问
as always you can leave me a question and I can answer it in the video
一如既往，你可以给我一个问题，我可以在视频中回答
just like I'm doing right now
就像我现在正在做的那样
thank you guys so much for watching take it easy
非常感谢你们观看，放轻松